Guide to the Ray Wu papers, [ca. 1966-2007]
Wu, Ray papers
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Progress in Nucleic Acid Research and Molecular Biology, Protein Expression and Purification, Nucleic Acids Research and Biochemistry, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints: Plant Cell Reports, Molecular and Cellular Biology, Transgenic Plants and Theoretical and Applied Genetics, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Plant Molecular Biology, Plant Molecular Biology and Nucleic Acids Research, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Biotechnology in Agriculture and Forestry, Molecular Biology and Evolution, Journal of Molecular Evolution and Gene Manipulation in Plant Improvement, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Molecular and General Genetics,The Plant Cell, Chromosoma and Plant Molecular Biology, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from The Plant Cell, Plant Molecular Biology, and Gene, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Plant Gene Transfer and Gene, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints: Theoretical and Applied Genetics, Plant Molecular Biology, Nucleic Acids Research and Plant Biotechnology, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Wu's Publications and Reprints from Plant Molecular Biology, Gene, Genes and Development, Molecular and Cellular Biology, Methods in Enzymology, Molecular and General Genetics, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences USA, Biochemistry and Theoretical and Applied Genetics, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Elson Chen, Mariam Stickeln, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Cao Yu, Nai Hu, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- CK He Plasmid Construct, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Plasmids To Be Constructed by P. Li, Li Yu etc, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- DBN Company, Beijing, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Forms and Correspondence: Linda Brainard, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003-2006 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Xing Guo Ye, You Zhi Ma, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Regarding Wheat Genes, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Forms and Correspondence: Research Agreement with Hong Ming Lam, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Forms and Correspondence: Qifa Zhang, Yongzhong Xing, 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Forms and Correspondence: Lizhong Xiong, Qifa Zhang, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Chengkun He, Steve Beer, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Zhaolong Wang, Bingru Huang, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Photographs and Correspondence: Zhong Qi Liu (Tianjin), 2005, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Photographs and Manuscripts: Zhing Qi Liu, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Yao Guang Liu, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Jian Kang Zhu, Yan Guo, Kwangwon Lee, Liming Xiong, 2003-2007 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Photographs and Correspondence Regarding TPSP Transgenic Rice, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Reports, Manuscripts and Gene Sequences: Rice Actin 2,3 (P), 1990, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Collaboration Agreement and Correspondence: Daniel Clark; Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Office Hardware Information and Manuals, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Cornell Wellness Program, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Forms: Employee Verification, ISSO, 1992, 2001, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Manuscripts and Newspaper Articles on Rice, 1997, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- TCM (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1997-2008 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Articles on Biofuels, 2001, 2006, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Useful Information - Cornell, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- "Science News and Articles", 1997-2007 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Crop Biotech Net; Agricultural Biology News Reports and Manuals, 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Biographies: Scientists (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Biotech Business News Reports (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Articles and News Reports: Genetically Modified Food (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Articles and News Reports: Plant Genomics, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Patenting Information, 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Stress Tolerant Plants, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- "Plasmids Sent Out", 2001-2008 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Articles and News Reports: Rice, 2004-2007 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Books (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Articles and News Reports: Stem Cell Research, 2002-2007 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- China: Agricultural News Reports (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Database Subscriptions, 1994, 1995, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Hui Jiang, Micheal Hayes, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: David McElroy, Rajinder Jain, 2003-2007 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Articles and News Reports: Human Genome Project, 1991-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Articles, Books and Prints Related to Patenting, 1999-2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Jukon Kim, 1998-2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Reports: Jayaprakash Targolli, Veena Hedatale, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Slides; Scanning Manuals, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- DNA Preparation; Undergraduate Laboratory Manual, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Laboratory Methods, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Laboratory Methods, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Laboratory Methods, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Undergraduate Laboratory Manual, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Useful Laboratory Methods, 1994-1995, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Laboratory Methods, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Laboratory Methods and Records, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Plasmids To Be Constructed, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Useful Laboratory Methods, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Useful Laboratory Methods, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Laboratory Procedures, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, Manuscripts and Articles: Su May Yu, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Argobacterium, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- "Our Genome Project", 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Cultivation, Transplantation and Regeneration of Rice, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- GA (Small) Group Meeting, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Articles, News Reports and Manuscripts: Plant Biotechnology, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Manuscripts and Articles, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Rodrigues Proposal, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Recovered Rice RFCP Probes, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Plasmid Requests, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Transgenic Maize, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Travel Documents, 1995-1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Correspondence: Wu Hong; Manuscript and Photographs: CUSBEA Article, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Chinese Consulate, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Correspondence: T. D. Lee, Chen Ning Yang, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Yi Sun, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Articles and News Reports: Stem Cell Research (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Stem Cell Institute Discussion, July 2007 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Albert Kausch, 2003-2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Correspondence and Permits for Shipments: Kan Wang, Iowa State University, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Silvia Wu, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- AAAS Fellow, CALS Award, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Cheung Kong Scholars Programme, 1999-2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Wu Jiaping, 2004-2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Wu Jiaping, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Liu Yao Guang, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Boston (RIP Antibody), Diego Breviario, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Rice Seeds; Plasmid Requests, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Sony Computer order, July 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Lui LI Fei, Mike Cohen (IRRI), 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Yun-Bi Xu, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Su May Yu, 1999-2003 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Molecular Cloning, 3rd Edition, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- "Plasmids We Sent Out", 2001-2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Correspondence and Reports: GNA CPTi, Axis Genetics Ltd., 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- "Plasmids We Received", 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Arabidopsis and Other Genomes (Box 17, Folder 20)
- REMOVED Undergraduate Assistants, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Kenny Lang, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Department Candidates, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Correspondence and Reports: Department of Molecular Biology and Genetics, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- "Seminars; Permanent Letters", 2007 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Seminars, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Correspondence and Agreement Forms: Glorious Sun Group, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Liyam Ping, Wu Nai Hu, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Requests for Plasmids, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Requests for Rice Seeds, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Invitations to Meetings, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Meeting Notices, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Correspondence and Agreement Forms: Glorious Sun Group, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Useful Notes, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Wu Fellowship Recipients, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, Publications, News Reports and Dissertations, 1989-2005 (Box 18)
  Dissertations include those from Indian institute of Science, National Chung Hsing University, Taiwan, Academia Sinica, Taiwan, Purdue university, University of California at Santa Barbara and Cornell University, Publications include Agro Food Hitech, AgBiotech '98, The CAAS Journal, China Science and Technology Newsletter, Committee of Hundred Survey, The Rice Foundation, The Plant Journal, Plant Physiology, Texas Rice, IRRI Research Notes, Rice Today, Chinese Rice Research Newsletter, Engineering Science Quarterly, Chinese Academy of Engineers Newsletter and Plant Molecular Biology. Correspondence includes that with China Bridges International, CALS Faculty, Cornell Life Sciences Institute, Jerry Yang, Gu Xiaocheng, etc.
- USDA and NSF Grant Information, 2000-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- NSF Grant Information, Plant Genome Project, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- NSF Grant information; Related Manuscripts, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- NSF Grant information, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Administrative Documents, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- NSF Electronic Proposal Submission Manual, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- "Useful Methods" (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Manuscripts and Publications, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Manuscripts and Publications, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Chine Bridges International, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- HIV/AIDS: China's Titanic Peril, UNAIDS Report, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Recombinant DNA, Second Edition, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Chinese Science/University Publications, 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Cornell Publications; Laboratory Teaching Aids, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Genetic Methods, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Cornell China Program, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Radiation Safety Manual (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Radiation Safety Regulations and Procedures (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Biosafety Rules: China, India, Nigeria (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Vancouver Poster, May 1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- List of Conferences: Conferences Jaques Monod; Poster: Chinese Society of Bioscientists in America, 1992, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- DNA Sequencing (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Publications: Chinese Science Press, Chinese Academy of Sciences (Box 19, Folder 23)
- News Reports and Publications: Rice, 1989-2006 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Rice Biotechnology Quarterly, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Rice Biotechnology Quarterly, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- UNIDO/ICGB Report, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- A Brief history of the CUSBEA Program, March 2006 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Rice Biotechnology Quarterly; ACB, 1993, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Meeting Minutes, Agendas and Publications: CALS, January 1999 - April 1999 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Plant Molecular Biology Research at Cornell University, Annual Report: Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, Sharkstooth Comb, 1991, 2001, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Assorted Publications, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Ray Wu Society for Life Sciences;Agricultural and Life Sciences News; Miscellaneous Documents, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Journals: China historical Materials of Science and Technology, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Asia Pacific Biotech News, March 1999 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Conferences on life Sciences for the 21st Century; Methods in Enzymology, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Abstracts: Ray Wu Symposium, 70th Birthday Celebrations, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- PIs in the PKU: Yale Joint Research centre of plant molecular Genetics and Agrobiotechnology, 2006 (Box 19)
- Laboratory manual for Physiological Studies of Rice, 1976 (Box 19)
- Chinese Book (DCB), July 1994 (Box 19)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Zhang Hui, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- News Reports, Articles, Publications: "Reprints of Useful Material", 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Biology, Molecular and Cell Biology (BMCB) at Cornell University, 12 November 2007 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Biology, Molecular and Cell Biology (BMCB) at Cornell University, 12 November 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Articles and Publications: "Covers and Reprints to Save", 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Correspondence and Manuscript: Ping Liyan, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Nominations to Membership of Academia Sinica, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Correspondence and Edited Manuscripts: Y. G. Liu, Mark Jane, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Yao Guang Liu, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Kexuan Tang, February 2007 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Manuscripts: Hang et al, January 2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- International Professor Appointment, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Academia Sinica, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Plant molecular Biology Reporter, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Chinese Contributions to America: An International Academic Conference, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Chang Jiang Scholars Program, 2002-2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Manuscript: Shi Hong Zhang, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Centenary Celebration: Chinese Agricultural University, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Intellectual Property Strategy, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- International Service for the Acquisition of Agri-Biotech Applications, 2000, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Biopolis (Singapore) Information Booklet, October 2002 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Nominations to Membership of Academia Sinica, 2001-2007 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Documents (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Proceedings of the Second US-Korea Joint Seminar on Plant Molecular Genetics and Breeding, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Correspondence: Academia Sinica, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Soo Chen Chang, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Manuscript: Salt Tolerance (Box 21, Folder 2)
- China Agricultural University Centennial, September 2005 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Biochemistry Laboratory Equipment Product Guides, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Ray Wu Society, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Chinese News and Biochemistry Articles, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- List of Articles on Computer Storage, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- News Articles and Publications: Financing and Education; Impact Factor, 2000-2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Chinese Biological Investigators Society (CBIS), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- CBIS Symposium; "My Visits to China", July 2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Ray Wu Society/CBIS, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Members: Ray Wu Society/CBIS, 1998, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Publications: National Institute of Biological Sciences, Beijing, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Publications: Dan Luo, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Manuscript: Tomohiro Kurai, August 2007 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Patents; Web Site, 2004-2007 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Appointment: Ming Chu Shih; Agricultural Biotechnology Research Centre (ABRC), Academia Sinica, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- MBG Strategic Planning Retreat, November 2007 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Hongyon Fu, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Lin Nu Sheng, June 2006 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- REMOVED Correspondence and manuscripts: Lin Nu Sheng, September 2006 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Shun Mei Liang, August 2006 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Photographs: DNA Extraction (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Brochures and Publications: Advanced Technologies (Cambridge) Ltd., Groupe Limagrain, Rural Development Administration, Korea, 1992, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Correspondence and Reports: Academia Sinica, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Laches Case, Albert Wai-Kit Chan, Cooper and Dunham Co., July 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Correspondence and Manuscripts: Robert Yu, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Meeting: Plant Tissue Culture at Cornell, 8 December 1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Apomixis Research Service, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Publications, 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- South China Agricultural University, March 2003 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Manual: Department of Biochemistry, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- IRRI: Directory, International Rice Congress, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- China Energy Conservation Project (Box 21)
- China EMC Market Reports (Box 21)
- International High Level Forum on Bioeconomy, March 2005 (Box 21)
- 5th international Rice Genetics Symposium and 3rd International Rice Functional Genomics Symposium, November 2005 (Box 21)
- Annual Report: Applera Corporation, 2006 (Box 21)
- General Meeting of the international program on Rice Biotechnology, September 1999 (Box 21)
- Arabidopsis thaliana Nucleic Acid Sequences, 1995 (Box 21)
- IRRI Highlight 1986, 1986 (Box 21)
- National Taiwan University, 1995 (Box 21)
- Lectures on Flower Development, Instituto Juan March de Estudios e Investigaciones, 1995 (Box 21)
- IRRI: International Rice Research: 25 Years of Partnership, 1985 (Box 21)
- Plant Biotechnology Research for Developing Countries, 1992 (Box 21)
- Basic Research on the Physiological Basis of High Yield, High Efficiency and Resistance to Stress in main Crops (Box 21)
- Research Report: Chengkun He, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Progressive Report: Pinghua Li, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- File Cabinet Items, April 2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Ray's Computer, November 2007 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Laboratory Report: Mayank Rai, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Cornell University publications: Great Ideas, Genetics and Development, Graduate Studies in Biochemistry, Molecular and Cell Biology, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- IRRI: Technical Bulletin 4: The Morphology and Varietal Characteristics of the Rice Plant, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Correspondence and manuscripts: Yi Rao, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Nanobiotechnology Center, Cornell University, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Manuscript: Telomere Research and Jack W. Szoztak, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Journals and Publications: The Plant Journal, Journal of Biology, 1991-1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Cornell Plant Breeding: China Cooperation (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Articles and Publications: Transformations, 2003-2006 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Publications and Reprints: RNA Slicing, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Publications and reprints: Gene Slicing, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- CUSBA - Bob Yu, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- 8th Annual Nanobiotechnology Symposium, Cornell University, October 2007 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- U.S. Patents, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Instructions for Journals; Impact Factors (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Lu Hong; Manuscripts: Rice QTL Mapping, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Publications and Manuscripts: Jian Kang Zhu, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Seed Industry: DBN Group (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Biweekly Report: Zhang Ling, 2005-2007 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Zhang Hongwei, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Reports: Zhengge Zhu, 2005-2007 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Reports: Chengkun He, July 2006 - October 2006 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Reports: Chengkun He, November 2006 - August 2007 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Reports: Zhihong Lin, May 2005 - July 2007 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Reports: Zhihong Lin, July 2007 - December 2007 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Reports: Mayank Rai, April 2006 - October 2007 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Reports: Long Xi Yu, February 2007 - November 2007 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Information on Fertilizers, Sea Water Composition, Greenhouse Maintenance (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Reprints: Rice - General Information (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Thesis: Hui Jiang, 10 September 2007 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Notes and Reprints: Rice - TKS, TNG 67, IRRI (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Reprints: Values and Products of Rice, Wheat and Maize (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Reports: Jerry Yang - Proposal to China, January 2007 - July 2007 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- People Working with Rice (Box 23, Folder 14)
- USDA Economic Statistics, September 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Jerry Yang, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Reprints, Photographs and Correspondence: Jerry Yang, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Reports, Catalogues, Reprints, Abstracts, Publications, Journals and Lecture Material (Box 24)
  Reports include those by the Cornell Genomics Initiative Task Force, Maw Ye and Valerie Jean Karpus. Publications and journals include Proceedings of the 22nd Rice Technical Working Group, Nutritional Disorders of the Rice Plant in Asia, National Health Research Institutes (China), Plant Molecular Genetics and Breeding, Biotechnology in China, Reminiscences and Perspectives (Academia Sinica), Prioritizing the Rice Biotechnology Research Agenda for Eastern India, Institute of Botany (Academia Sinica), etc. Abstracts include those from the 4th International Rice Functional Genomics Symposium, Molecular Biology in the 21st Century (Academia Sinica), Plant Molecular Biology Association Conference, 2nd International Symposium of Rice Functional Genomics, etc. Reprints include SRI - the System of Rice Intensification a glossary of plant terms and miscellaneous journal articles. Lecture material includes notes and slides for BioBM 737.
- Reprints of Journal Articles, 1959-1984, 1997-1999 (Box 25)
  Reprints of articles authored/co-authored by Ray Wu from Molecular Biology, Plant Molecular Biology, Gene, Genes and Development, Molecular and Cellular Biology, Methods in Enzymology, Molecular and General Genetics, Biochemistry, The Journal of Biological Chemistry, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences USA, Nature, Science, Journal of Virology, Nucleic Acids Research, Gene Function, Biotechnology in Agriculture and Forestry, Plant Biotechnology, Plant Physiology etc.
- Notes, Reports and Reprints: Post Doctoral Candidates, 1975-1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- BS 330 Problem Sets, April 1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Notes and Lecture Material: BioBM 737, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Rotation Report: Min Hue Chen, February 1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Seminar Notes: Shanghai; Lecture Material and Slides, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 5)